

# Web Developer

Southampton | +44 07388 649044 | cristiano\_santos93@hotmail.com | www.cristianocodes.net

#### **CAREER SUMMARY:**

I am a trilingual and highly motivated recent bachelor's degree recipient with more than 10 years of experience working in a team in different industries in different countries looking to kickstart my career in Web Development.

During my course, the design and development of an app was very interesting and I found myself having fun doing it. Interested in further developing my JavaScript and React skills to create even better projects. Currently located in Southampton, UK but willing to relocate as necessary.

Looking to kick start my career in Web Dev.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

## Bidvest Noonan | Southampton

Dishwasher - Teaml Leader | February, 2020 - Present

- Work as part of a team to insure all dishes and cutlery is clean and ready to use.
- Insure all machines are working properly and report any faults to the relevant Supervisor.
- Was able to quickly adapt to the role and after about 1 year was promoted to team leader.

## Showcase Cinema de Lux | Southampton

Usher | October, 2019 - August, 2021

- Worked as part of a team greeting the customers to check their tickets and providing the
  best possible service to make their cinema experience positive and memorable by
  clarifying any questions the customers had.
- On busy weekend days, handled over 100 customers

#### Johann Volonte AG | Nunningen, Solothurn

Building Construction / Bricklayer | August, 2016 - July, 2019

- Worked as part of a team in buildings construction and road repairs.
- Worked in a 2 man team in the removal and then renewal of the water pipelines in a Retirement Home.
- Handled communications when working with private customers.

## Arifi Naturstein AG | Reinach, Basel-Stadt

Auxiliary Worker | November, 2014 - July, 2016

Worked as part of a small team to build walls, floors and other stone related jobs.

# **SKILLS:**

- Front-end and back-end web development.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJs.
- UX/UI Design

## **EDUCATION:**

# 2019 - 2022 Southampton Solent University

BSc (Hons) Computing

## Learned:

- Problem Solving though Programming,
- UX,
- Web Technologies,
- Web App development,
- Human Computer Interaction,
- and much more.

# 2012 Escola Serafim Leite, Sao Joao da Madeira

Technical Renewable Energies and Solar Systems

# **INTERESTS:**

- Interested in Meta and often enjoy using my Meta Quest 2 device.
- A fan of Airsoft where I enjoy a nice day of exercise with friends.